<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EstimateX</string>
    <string name="sample">
        5.0269,    -2.6807;\n
        5.0365,    5.7014;\n
        5.0546,    3.8166;\n
        5.0594,    2.8214;\n
        5.0702,    5.1337;\n
        5.1077,    2.0576;\n
        5.1301,    0.5608;\n
        5.1793,    -0.7428;\n
        5.1884,    0.2042;\n
        5.2524,    -1.2200;\n
        5.3054,    1.9869;\n
        5.3077,    1.8396;\n
        5.3794,    3.5129;\n
        5.4069,    0.5566;\n
        5.4369,    0.6170;\n
        5.4901,    4.2630;\n
        5.4994,    1.0173;\n
        5.5204,    0.1520;\n
        5.5277,    9.1302;\n
        5.5416,    1.0179;\n
        5.5649,    3.0825;\n
        5.6063,    3.3928;\n
        5.6397,    4.6042;\n
        5.6407,    0.7162;\n
        5.7077,    1.8451;\n
        5.7107,    3.2522;\n
        5.7292,    0.4795;\n
        5.7340,    3.1551;\n
        5.7737,    2.4406;\n
        5.8014,    1.8440;\n
        5.8598,    6.8233;\n
        5.8707,    7.2029;\n
        5.8918,    1.8495;\n
        6.0020,    0.9270;\n
        6.0062,    1.2784;\n
        6.1101,    17.5920;\n
        6.1891,    3.1386;\n
        6.2742,    2.4756;\n
        6.3261,    5.1875;\n
        6.3328,    1.4233;\n
        6.3534,    5.4974;\n
        6.3557,    0.6786;\n
        6.3589,    -1.4211;\n
        6.3654,    5.3048;\n
        6.4296,    3.6518;\n
        6.4862,    6.5987;\n
        6.5159,    5.3436;\n
        6.5479,    0.2968;\n
        6.5894,    5.9966;\n
        6.8825,    3.9115;\n
        7.0032,    11.8540;\n
        7.0708,    5.3893;\n
        7.0931,    1.0463;\n
        7.2182,    4.8852;\n
        7.2259,    3.3411;\n
        7.3345,    4.0259;\n
        7.4239,    4.2885;\n
        7.4764,    4.3483;\n
        7.5386,    3.8845;\n
        7.5402,    6.7504;\n
        7.6031,    4.9981;\n
        7.6366,    4.2959;\n
        7.8247,    6.7318;\n
        7.9334,    4.5623;\n
        8.0959,    4.1164;\n
        8.2111,    6.5426;\n
        8.2934,    0.1445;\n
        8.2951,    5.7442;\n
        8.3829,    11.8860;\n
        8.4084,    7.2258;\n
        8.5172,    4.2415;\n
        8.5186,    13.6620;\n
        8.5781,    12.0000;\n
        8.8254,    5.1694;\n
        9.1802,    6.7981;\n
        9.2482,    12.1340;\n
        9.3102,    3.9624;\n
        9.4536,    5.4141;\n
        9.7687,    7.5435;\n
        10.1360,   6.6799;\n
        10.2360,   7.7754;\n
        10.2740,   6.7526;\n
        10.9570,   7.0467;\n
        11.7000,   8.0043;\n
        11.7080,   5.3854;\n
        12.8280,   13.5010;\n
        12.8360,   10.1170;\n
        13.1760,   14.6920;\n
        13.3940,   9.0551;\n
        14.1640,   15.5050;\n
        14.9080,   12.0540;\n
        18.9450,   22.6380;\n
        18.9590,   17.0540;\n
        20.2700,   21.7670;\n
        20.3410,   20.9920;\n
        21.2790,   17.9290;\n
        22.2030,   24.1470;
    </string>
    <string name="manual">
        EstimateX is used to train the machine to generate a hypothesis on the basis of a given training set. This hypothesis will help you to estimate the desired entity for any set of parameters.
        \n\nFor example, if you want to sell a particular house in a city, but before selling it you want to estimate the price of this house in order to avoid attaining a loss.
        \nLet us assume that the price of a house depends only on it\'s area (size). Hence you need to provide a data set (training set) consisting of sizes of some random houses in the city along with their respective prices to the machine.
        \n\nThe input-format of training set for this application is as follows :
        \nparameter1,parameter2,....,parameterN,trainingValue1;
        \nparameter1,parameter2,....,parameterN,trainingValue2;
        \n.\n.\n.
        \nparameter1,parameter2,....,parameterN,trainingValueM;
        \n\nHere let us consider 3 training examples to estimate the price of our house :
        \n\n 100,2500000;
        \n 200,4500000;
        \n 250,5500000;
        \n\n Inorder to estimate a value corresponding to certain parameters after providing the training set, you need to input those parameters in this application as follows:
        \n\n parameter1,parameter2,....,parameterN;
        \n\n Here let us consider the size of our house to be 150. As our estimation is only based on a single parameter, our input to the machine will be as follows :
        \n\n150;
        \n\nAfter proving the training set and estimation parameters, you need to set the power of this estimation. Power of the estimation will be the degree of your hypothesis.
        \n\n Note : HIGH VALUE OF POWER GIVES RISE TO THE PROBLEM OF \'OVERFITTING\'. HENCE, KEEPING THE VALUE OF POWER LESS THAN 4 IS RECOMMENDED. THE DEFAULT VALUE IS 1 (LINEAR HYPOTHESIS).
        \n\n After setting the power of estimation, in order to let machine generate a hypothesis for your estimation, you need to click ESTIMATE button.
        \n Doing this you will see the estimated value on your screen.
        \n\n If your training set comprises of only one parameter (same as in this example), you can plot your hypothesis as well as training example on a cartesian plane by clicking on the PLOT HYPOTHESIS button.

        \n\n IMPORTANT INSTRUCTIONS
        \n\n 1) Strictly follow the input format mentioned above for both training set as well as estimation parameters or the application may not function properly.
        \n\n 2) Do not miss any commas (,) or semi-colons (;) while providing the input to the machine.
        \n\n 3) All the inputs strictly have to be numeric. Do not use any other character in your inputs. Or it may cause the application to malfunction.
        \n\n 4) Try to avoid using high values of power of estimation.
    </string>

    <string-array name="powerChoices">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>9</item>
        <item>10</item>

    </string-array>

</resources>